【家长提示】本片的评级为 TV-14-DLV，
可能包含暗示性对话、粗俗语言和暴力等内容，
因而不建议 14 岁以下儿童独自观赏。
做好准备  一场视觉盛宴即将开始
Get ready to turn your brains to viewing mode
因为  在上一集的《终空》里
because, previously on "Final Space,"
终空     前情提要
盖瑞竟然收到了来自奎恩的求救信号
Gary just received a Mayday call for none other than Quinn,
没错  就是那位盖瑞五年来
the super-spicy captain he hasn't stopped
一直朝思暮想的火辣队长
thinking about for the past five years.
真是惨案啊  哈哈哈
What a loser! Ha ha ha!
对了  听说无疆守护还在追捕奎恩？
Oh, and Quinn is on the run from the Infinity Guard?
哇  这就很刺激了
Whoa! We've had our fun.
你也来感受一下？
Get ready to have yours.
盖瑞  你的氧气还够用6分钟
Gary, you have six minutes of oxygen left.
不是吧
It can't be.
你在做什么  盖瑞？
What are you doing, Gary?
你觉得我像在做什么？
What do you think I'm doing?
我要摄取它的能量
I'm gonna consume its power.
但是  一旦打开头盔  你的内脏将会胀裂
But opening your helmet will blow out your internals,
从而导致瞬间死亡
inducing instantaneous death.
那只是一种可能性
That's one possible outcome.
另一种可能性  我吃掉了饼干
Another, I eat the cookie,
然后它的能量使我变成一头雄伟的  能在太空呼吸的蝎狮
and its power turns me into a majestic space-breathing manticore.
※蝎狮（manticore）是波斯传说中的生物，形象为人头、狮身、蝎尾，并会将对方整个吃下
你将会在吃下饼干前死亡
You will die before you eat the cookie.
我死之前绝对吃得上饼干
I'm pretty sure I could get it in there before I die.
这是不可能的  盖瑞
That is not possible, Gary.
我真的感觉我吃得上
I really think I can do it.
只要把它慢慢捞进来  然后迅速合上头盔就好了
I'm gonna lob it right in and close the helmet super fast.
你做不到的  盖瑞
You can't, Gary.
捞不进  合不上  吃不到
No lobbing, no closing, no cookie.
Translated by @SerCom_KC
OPEN TRANSLATION PROJECT
求救  求救
Mayday, Mayday!
我叫奎恩·艾冈  无疆守护的一名队长
My name is Quinn Airgone, a captain in the Infinity Guard.
Translated by @SerCom_KC
OPEN TRANSLATION PROJECT
我在追查引力干扰的来源
I've been investigating a gravitational disturbance,
目前得出的结论是太空出现了一个缺口
which I now see is a breach in space.
翻译版本
v1.0.0-CHS
很多人因此而死
Many people are dead,
光折失效
再这样下去我迟早也会…
and I'm about to join them unless this...
光折失效
翻译
SerCom_KC
呱呱鴨
Aah!
就没有哪个白痴能够听到我的求救信号吗？
Is there not a single idiot that can hear me?!
我听得到啊
I can hear her.
校对
万俟猫
宇宙史上最伟大的爱情故事
The greatest love story in the history of the universe
校对
旗木佐罗
即将开花结果
is about to blossom forth.
哎  老兄  别那么激动啊
Yo, dude, just keep the expectations in check.
时间轴
SerCom_KC
这五年来  奎恩从来就没有回过你消息吧
Quinn hasn't responded to a single message of yours in five years.
特效
SerCom_KC
大家都很忙的  我就很忙
People get busy. I'm busy.
你还能忙上五年？
For five years?
是4年11个月又30天
4 years, 11 months and 30 days.
那不就是五年
That's five years, bro.
也许是  也许不是
Maybe it is. Maybe it isn't.
明明就是
It is.
但也可以不是啊
But it could not be.
已成功锁定失控运输机
Disabled transporter is now locked in.
即将派遣机器人展开对奎恩的救援
Dispatching SAMES to secure Quinn.
S A M E S
不要跟我抢  HUE！
Over my hard nipples, HUE!
能救奎恩的只有我船长一个人
If anyone is saving Quinn, it's me, the captain.
盖瑞  这已经是第9045次了
Gary, for what is the 9,045th time,
目前你仍然是一个囚犯
you are still a prisoner.
不对
I disagree.
事情的严重性迟早会是星际范围的
As soon as the crap hit the interstellar fan,
到那个时候  我就是真正的船长了
I became the captain for real.
计算结果…否定
Calculating... no.
计算结果  肯定
Calculating, yes.
我要动用我的权力拯救奎恩
I will use those powers to rescue Quinn.
翻译项目地址
translatedby.sercomkc.org/finalspace
你的刑期再延长一个星期
One week has been added to your sentence.
妈的还…还…还…还会说啥  HUE？
Frickin' what... what... w... what's new, HUE?
本翻译作品按照CC BY-NC-SA 4.0许可协议向公众授权
未经授权禁止用于任何商业用途
你还会说啥？
What's new?
所以  在我拼尽全力拯救我爱的女人之前
Now, before I risk my life for the woman I love,
如您喜欢本作品
请通过官方渠道购买正版周边以示支持
www.starcadet.com/collections/final-space
谁手上有粒薄荷糖？
does anyone perchance have a breath mint?
我有  盖瑞
Right here, Gary.
Ach! Oh!
天啊  不好  我的好朋友要死了
God, no, I'm killing my best friend!
让我KVN帮你取出来  我来就好
Let KVN get it. I can do it.
很快就好了  就在这里
I'm close. It's right there.
哇  KVN  赶紧滚  滚得越远越好
Whoa, KVN, stay away, far away from me forever!
老天  啊！
Oh, my God! Ugh!
Aah!
船体严重受损
立即弹射
开始救援
Commencing rescue.
开始命运
Commencing destiny.
干得好  我要征用你的飞船
Nice work. I need to commandeer your ship.
我有一个三级重要事项要做
I have a class-three priority.
奎恩
Quinn,
你的那份火辣真是不减当年啊
you look every bit as spicy as the last time I saw you.
哦  你叫什么来着？
Great, and you are again?
Oh-ho-ho!
我真怀念你那锋利的眼光啊
How I've missed your razor-sharp wit.
不  说真的  我不认识你
No, seriously, I have no idea who you are.
真的吗？
Really?
一点都没有面熟的感觉
You resemble no one I know,
所以  真的不认识
so, yeah, really.
不是开玩笑？
Seriously?
不是开玩笑
Seriously.
饿地神啊  看来你深受健忘症之扰
Oh, dear Lord, you're suffering from amnesia!
真正困扰我的是一个即将毁灭地球的紧急情况
I'm suffering from an emergency that's going to destroy Earth.
奎恩  你真以为我相信你把我忘了？
Quinn, you really expect me to believe you don't know who I am?
等下  我知道要怎么让你“记得”我
Hold on. I know how to fix this.
这才是真正的盖瑞
This is the real raw Gary.
这招没用的  是谁都没用
That didn't fix it, whoever you are.
心如刀割啊
What a dagger to the heart.
我已经变成了一个整整五年
I'm the guy who, for the past five years,
每天都在向一个不认识我的女人
has been sending daily documentaries
发送每日记录的家伙吗
to the woman who has no idea who I am!
哇  这也太惨了吧  我真的一条都没有收到
Wow, that sucks. I never got any of them.
不过  可以先带我去主控室吗…
Now, if you could just show me where the bridge is...
没关系的  毕竟这就是人生啊
It's all good. Life, you know?
嗯  是好人没错  可惜有问题  很有问题
Hmm, cute guy, but issues, definite issues.
奎恩连我是谁都认不出了
Quinn doesn't even know who I am!
Oh, no! Oh!
Oh! Uh!
啊…怎么会这样啊
Oh... this is not what it's supposed to be.
我的天啊  心好痛啊
Oh, God, it hurts so much!
啊  她连我是谁都不知道
Oh, she doesn't even know who I am!
我要把我的感受录下来
I need to record my feelings!
奎恩  如果你看得到这段录像的话
Quinn, for future reference,
假装自己健忘这件事情其实无可厚非
the decent thing would've been to fake amnesia.
我会假装自己健忘
I would've faked amnesia.
我认识和我所爱的人都会假装自己健忘
People I know and love all would've faked amnesia,
但是  我们说实在话
but you had to be honest.
请你举出一种彼此完全坦诚相待的关系
Name one decent relationship that has ever been built on honesty.
举不出来对不对
You can't, can you?
因为这种关系根本就不存在
That's because there aren't any.
我知道我说的都是胡话
I know this doesn't make any sense,
但我真的想跟别人聊一聊
but I really needed to talk to somebody right now,
而你是唯一一个能够让我打开感情的钱包
and you're the only person I can open my heart wallet to
倾倒痛苦的硬币的人
and spend my hurt coins with.
杰瑞？
Jerry?
Oh!
杰瑞？你连我的名字都不知道了
Jerry? You don't even know my name.
阿瓦卡多  他还好吗？
Avocato, is he all right?
一点都不
No.
你知道阿瓦卡多的名字？
You know Avocato's name?
大家好啊
Hey, gang.
别来搞事  KVN
Not now, KVN.
卡尔  汉克  奥尔森  面条
Carl, Hank, Orson, Noodles,
能不能让我和…
can you give me and, uh...
盖瑞
Gary.
…盖瑞  单独聊一聊？
...Gary a minute?
这个录像是给谁看的？
Who are you recording that for?
一个对我来说很重要的人
Someone who meant quite a lot to me.
但愿她终有一天能看到吧
I hope she gets to see it one day.
在这么遥远的太空之中  人确实很容易迷惘
When you're this far out in space, most of that stuff gets lost.
看来是这样  你为啥要来这里？
Suppose it does. What did you come here for?
我只是想说  “谢谢你  盖尔德”
I just wanted to say, "Thank you, Gerald."
不客气
You're welcome.
盖尔德？他是叫盖尔德吗？
Gerald? Is his name Gerald?
原来他一直都在说谎？
Was he lying to us this whole time?
我有点晕  盖尔德可能是小名吧
I'm confused. Maybe Gerald is a nickname.
也许他的姓是盖尔德
Maybe his last name is Gerald.
能解释一下吗  盖尔德  盖瑞  盖尔德
Help me to understand, Gerald, Gary, Gerald.
这艘飞船现已受到无疆守护当局的控制
This ship has been seized by the authority of the Infinity Guard.
卡尔  别来烦我  我今天心情很不好
Carl, not right now. I've had a bad day.
我现在不想要抱抱  卡尔
I am really not in the mood for a hug, Carl.
卡尔  够了  我没事
Carl, that's enough. I'm fine.
别来搞我！
Get away from me!
卡尔坏！卡尔坏！
Bad Carl! Bad Carl!
卡尔坏坏！
Bad Carl!
紧急状况  我们的动力反应堆已被耗尽
Emergency. Our power reactor has been drained.
紧急锁闭
银河一号目前无法移动
The Galaxy One is immobilized.
紧急锁闭
我的系统已经被上传了接管命令
A takeover command has been uploaded into my system.
我已经在尽力抵抗了  但它迟早会被执行
I am fighting it, but it will succeed.
好吧  啊
Okay. Uh.
是无疆守护  我们被黑了
It's the Infinity Guard. We've been hacked.
不知道为什么  他们想中断我的调查
For some reason, they're trying to shut down my investigation.
一群呆瓜
What a bunch of nerds.
他们是冲着我来的
They're after me.
你？为啥啊？你那么完美
You? Why? You're perfect.
要我怎么说呢
Where do I start?
地球正在一点一点被黑洞吞噬
The Earth is being sucked into a black hole.
然后我离了队  偷了一艘飞船  逃过了逮捕
I went rogue, stole a ship, evaded arrest,
要是我现在不离船  所有人都会死
and if I don't get off this ship, everyone dies.
你这只老狐狸
You sly fox.
妈呀  好吧
Oh, my gosh. Okay.
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
我想说的是  你这个寒冰女王
I meant, "You icy minx."
啊  我流血了  我流血了
Oh, I'm bleeding! I'm bleeding.
抱歉  我想说  危险的熊猫？
Sorry, I meant, "Danger panda?"
喔  我们在打情骂俏欸
Oh! We're flirting!
打情骂俏啊！太好了！
We're flirting! This is great!
我们的关系又要进一步…
This is a good advancement in our relation--
妈呀  好吧好吧  我们不闹了
Oh, my gosh! Okay. Okay. We're done flirting.
我们不闹了
We're not flirting,
想起以前了
just like old times.
真的  这还只是个开始
Trust me. This is just the start.
很快就会有一艘绝统巡航船来逮捕全飞船的人
An Imperium cruiser will be on the way to seize the ship.
那就欢迎上船啰  说得好像我们麻烦还不够多一样
Well, welcome aboard. Like we needed more danger.
等到无疆守护的人过来  我们干脆束手就擒吧
Now we're just stuck here until the Infinity Guard captures us.
我们要怎样才能使这趟飞驰的火车重回正轨？
How do we get this choo-choo train back to Safetytown?
理论上  我们可以利用那颗垂死恒星的光线
Theoretically, we could harness the solar rays from that dying star,
即将演化成
超新星
但它非常不稳定
but it is highly unstable.
即将演化成
超新星
我们必须离开这片区域
We've got to get out of here.
即将演化成
超新星
我可以用VX-1光物泵做一次太空跳
I could space-vault close enough to it with a VX-1 light-matter pump,
光与物质
靠近后就开始采集  然后就能重启反应堆核心了
mine it and restart the reactor core.
我来
I'll do it.
我要再救你一次
I'll save you again.
想都别想
No way.
我就是想
Yes way.
就你？
You?
就我！
Me!
不行  不行  不行  必须是我
No, no, no, me.
不行不行！就是我！
No, not! Me!
我…就让我来好了
I... I will do it.
我一定要让你记住盖瑞·古斯比这个人
Then you will know who Gary Goodspeed is.
不用担心  这种事情我干多…
Don't worry. I do this all the tim--
这种事情他确实干多了
He does do that all the time.
我要拯救飞船
I'm gonna save the ship.
我要拯救奎恩
I'm gonna save Quinn.
我要驾驭这该死的命运
I'm gonna harness the crap out of destiny.
月饼  我们上
Mooncake, let's do this!
Choo, choo, choo, choo, woo-hoo!
放首好听的  HUE
Play the good stuff, HUE.
♫
Shelby Merry - Gallows
推进器可以使用
You're a go for thrusters.
I spent a year out in the desert
彳亍茫茫大漠中
I spent a year out in the sea
飘荡浩浩大海上
I spend my nights under the stars
每晚身披着星光
Just dreaming of sleep
却无法沉入梦乡
I still question where I've been
忆不起来自何方
发生了啥？
What is that?!
I don't know where I will go
亦不知身心所向
I just look up to the skies
唯有仰首望天空
曝光补偿
这颗恒星的周围是损毁飞行器的坟场
The star is surrounded by a graveyard of destroyed vessels.
曝光补偿
like there's a sign I didn't see, I didn't know
似有未曾见识过的征象
曝光补偿
谢谢提醒啊  HUE
Thank you for the heads-up, HUE.
盖瑞  你所看到的一切
What you are seeing, Gary,
正是“鲜红之矛”及其船队的残骸
is the remains of the Scarlet Lance and its fleet.
上千条生命葬身于此
Thousands of souls were lost.
而且这里很乱  这个还是看得出来的  HUE
And it's messy. We got that part, HUE.
这里乱成一团了
It's a mess all over here.
这里  还有那里  在我这个位置
There, over there, right here,
特别是这里  到处  都是乱的
especially right here, everywhere, it's a mess.
Chookity.
抓紧时间  盖瑞  恒星很快就要发生内爆了
Hurry, Gary. The star is about to implode.
Take me on down
引我前行吧
采集器已启动
开始了  HUE
We're cooking, HUE.
At the gallows it was mercy I had found
我的救赎在那绞刑架之上
能量接收中
Power is being received.
机器人正在切割大门
The SAMES are cutting through.
S A M E S
HUE系统已被控制
HUE system is overrun.
启发式统一实体
在场的所有人都是无疆守护的囚犯
You are all now prisoners of the Infinity Guard.
很快就会有一艘“绝统”前来逮捕你们
An Imperium will be here shortly to seize you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
在干嘛啊？
Whatcha doing?
没干嘛  不过是被你关在这里而已
Not much, you know, mostly being imprisoned.
看你长得一脸屎样
You look like crap.
给我闭嘴
Shut up!
一直都顶着这么一张屎脸
You always look like crap,
不过现在  你这脸简直就像屎上加粪
but right now, like, you look like if crap built a house on crap.
闭嘴闭嘴闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
噢  又来这套
Ah, come on!
吃啊
Enjoy.
机器人  逮捕目标
SAMES, apprehend the targets.
S A M E S
允许使用一切必要的武力
Use all force necessary.
我们攻进来只是时间问题
It is only a matter of time before we break in.
请立即投降
Surrender now.
如果我们能进到HUE的主机里
If we can get into HUE's mainframe,
我们就能重新获得对飞船的控制权
we can regain control of the ship.
啊  但是机器人挡住了去路啊
Ugh, the SAMES are blocking our way out.
S A M E S
那我们就自寻他路
That's our way out.
各位  我能关闭HUE系统
Hey, guys, I can disable HUE.
我们需要最靠谱的人来做这件事
We need to send the best person for the job.
那就我来吧
I accept.
我屁眼里有把钥匙
I have a key in my butthole.
我觉得我来比较好
I was thinking of me.
那就有意思了  我也觉得我来比较好
That's funny because I was thinking of me.
我做得到啦  信我一回好不好
I can do it. Embrace the KVN.
你甚至不是无疆守护的一员
You're not even part of the Infinity Guard.
可你是导致这场麻烦的祸因
You're the reason we're even in this mess,
而我能带领我们逃离险境
and I'm the reason we're going to get out of it.
懂了吗  宝贝？
Got that, baby?
不要  叫我  宝贝
Don't... call me... "baby."
还是祝我好运吧  大伙们
Wish me luck, guys.
KVN! KVN!
KVN! KVN! KVN!
船长日志5397
Captain's log 5397...
我们发现了一个小型生命体
We have found a life-form small in size.
博士们都说他们从没看到过这种生命体
The doctors tell me it's unlike anything they have ever seen.
我们称它为E-351
We're calling it E-351.
长官  有人请求与我们联络
Captain, we're being hailed.
接进来
Link it through.
你们好啊
Hello.
你们找到了我搜寻已久的东西
You found something I have been searching for.
把它交出来
Hand it over!
长官  他们正在登陆我们的舰艇
Captain, they're logging onto our fleet.
快启动光折引擎
Prepare the lightfold engines!
长官  他们开火了
Sir, they're firing!
全体找掩护…
Evasive...
Gah!
Chookity?
你给你走过的每一个地方都带去了死亡
Wherever you go, death follows,
就算是盖瑞  也难逃此劫
and it will make its way to Gary.
真是越来越热了啊  HUE…HUE！
It's getting pretty hot out here, HUE. HUE!
HUE？HUE  听得见吗？
HUE? HUE, can you hear me?
H.U.E.
离线
HUE？阿瓦卡多？
HUE? Avocato?
奎恩？有人吗？
Quinn? Anybody?!
KVN？
KVN?
好吧  反正也该回去了  不然这颗恒星就要内爆了
All right. Time to head back before this star implodes.
月饼呢？月饼！
Where's Mooncake? Mooncake!
盖瑞
Gary.
为啥那里有只毛毛虫呢？
Why is there a caterpillar out here?
为啥你离我脸这么近呢  小东西？
What brings you, noble creature, so close to my face?
等等  我为啥要和一只毛毛虫讲话？
Wait. Why am I talking to a caterpillar?
显然  我出现幻觉了
It's obvious. I'm hallucinating.
Aah!
Huh!
乖儿子  最近过得怎样？
How's my boy doing?
很好啊
Great.
爸？
Dad?
这不太对啊
That's unsettling.
全新的绝统T3巡航船
The new Imperium T3 Cruiser
将会带领我们开启下一个星系
will bridge us to the next galaxy,
倒计时准备
and the countdown has begun.
十
10...
嘿  想不想出去看发射啊
Hey, you want to watch the launch outside?
九
9...
肯定啊
You bet!
七
7...
六
6...
爸！
Dad!
五
5...
睁大眼睛看仔细喔
Keep your eyes open.
四
4...
它会从那个位置直冲云霄
It'll be taking off right over there.
三
3...
二
2...
一
1.
总有一天  我也要像他们一样
One day, I'm gonna do that.
想好啦？
You are, huh?
那当然  我要经历一连串的冒险
Yeah, I'm gonna have a whole bunch of adventures.
一连串吗？
A whole bunch?
而且要串串相连
Bunches and bunches.
为啥要给我看这个？
Why are you showing this to me?
回答我啊  你这毒害心灵的小虫！
Answer me, you drug-dealer caterpillar!
Ohhhh!
我记得这事
I remember this.
儿子
Son...
我要陪你一块儿去
I could come with you.
虽然你是我在这个世界上最疼爱的人
There's nothing more in the world that I would want,
但这次真的不行  小伙子
but not this time, little buddy.
这次我只能一个人去
I have to do this one alone.
可能你不会明白
You won't understand,
但要记住  我是为了你好
but know that I'm doing this for you.
可以答应我一件事吗？
Can you make me a promise?
好啊
Yeah.
答应我  你将踏上属于你自己的冒险之路
Promise me you'll have your own adventures.
我会的
I will.
而且要串串相连
Bunches and bunches.
拿着  我不在的时候  让这个小家伙陪着你
Here, this fellow will look after you while I'm gone.
它的名字是？
What's his name?
月饼
Mooncake.
我很清楚你要做什么  KVN
KVN, I know what you're trying to do, KVN.
像你这样的贱货是绝对无法关闭我的
Every attempt to disable me will fail because you are a loser.
恕难从命  HUE  我要把这玩意儿插进你主机里
Can't talk, HUE. I have to insert this thingy in you.
Huh!
我不会让你继续植入的
I will not let that insertion happen.
最后一次机会  请立即停止你的行为
This is your last chance to cease all action.
停下
Stop.
Ugh!
没有人会相信你的
No one believes in you.
放弃吧  你这个渣滓
Go back, you waste of life.
KVN  快啊
Hurry, KVN!
Oh, ah, ooh.
从备份数据启动中
Booting back up.
所有系统现已脱离无疆守护网络的控制
All systems now independent of the Infinity Guard network.
Aah! Aah!
KVN  赢了
KVN is victorious!
KVN成功了！做得好啊  KVN
KVN did it! Good job, KVN.
这事盖瑞打死都不会信的
Gary is never going to believe this.
系统已重启  你们好
Systems have been reactivated. Hello.
你回来了就好  HUE
Nice to have you back, HUE.
回来虽好
Nice to be back.
但原谅我哪壶不开提哪壶
Sorry to be the bearer of bad news,
我们仍处于极大的危险之中
but we're still in extreme danger.
那些无疆守护的混账们已经找到我们了
Those dickheads from the Infinity Guard found us,
然而盖瑞至今没有响应
and Gary is not responding.
你在哪  盖瑞？
Gary, where are you?
你能接受的辐射量值快要超标了
Your radiation levels are becoming critical.
立即离开那里
You must leave now.
约翰·古斯比此次的任务是
John Goodspeed is on a mission
调查造成太空异象的量子重力值变化的原因
to investigate a shift in the gravitational constant that's creating an anomaly in space.
我不想再看下去了
Don't make me watch this.
你必须看到最后
You have to.
爸！
Dad!
警告  警告
Warning, warning,
已达可接受之辐射量值的92%
radiation levels have reached 92%.
Chookity, pok, pok.
盖瑞  立即返回飞船
Gary, return to the ship immediately.
我侦测到了来自恒星内部的剧烈变化
I am detecting massive fluctuations in the star.
HUE  准备启动光折引擎
HUE, prime the lightfold engines.
那盖瑞怎么办？
What about Gary?
我们已经没有时间了
We don't have the time.
要是我被无疆守护抓到  数十亿人都会死的
If the Infinity Guard catches me, billions of people die.
虽然我喜欢杰瑞
I like Jerry.
是盖瑞
Gary.
对  盖瑞
Right, Gary.
我也不想丢下他  但这真的不是一个个体的问题
I don't want to leave him, but this is bigger than one person.
已达可接受之辐射量值的98%
Radiation levels have now reached 98%.
醒醒  盖瑞
Wake up, Gary.
恒星随时都有可能爆炸
The star could explode at any moment.
盖瑞  快点回到飞船上来啊
Gary, we need you to get back to the ship now!
盖瑞  恒星很快就要演化成超新星了
Gary, the star is going supernova.
盖瑞  你他妈的给我醒醒啊
Gary, wake the hell up, man.
赶紧回飞船  立刻马上
Get back to the ship pronto.
快啊
Come on.
妈妈咪啊
Oh, my gram!
再快点
Go faster!
快快快快快快快快快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Oh! Oh, oh!
天啊  这下麻烦了  噢不！
Oh, this is troubling! Oh, no!
他会赶不上的
He won't make it in time.
不  他可以的
Yes, he will.
抱歉了  奎恩  我们等盖瑞来
Sorry, Quinn. We wait for Gary.
好吧  我们等盖瑞来
All right. We wait for Gary.
已做好银河一号登船准备
Galaxy One, prepare to be boarded.
他妈的快给我开门！
Open the freaking door!
立即开始光折  HUE
Lightfold the ship, HUE!
泽塔克朗·阿尔法
“总司令”殖民地监狱
有了
It works.
爸  这是我所在的坐标
Dad, these are my coordinates.
快来找我  我不指望你能马上来
Come find me, I mean, at your leisure,
但可以的话  能早一点来是最好
but, like, for me, preferably fast. That'd be great.
爸  这是我所在的坐标
Dad, these are my coordinates.
快来找我  我不指望你能马上来
Come find me, I mean, at your leisure,
但可以的话  能早一点来是最好
but, like, for me, preferably fast. That'd be great.
重置HUE跟机器人的人是谁来着？
Who reverse-hacked HUE and the SAMES again?
S A M E S
我啊
I did.
当我们就听你一个人的啊
Right, you keep saying that,
你根本就不可能的好吧
except there's just no way that's possible.
我就说吧
Oh, yeah. He's truthin' it.
话说  能不能跟我讲讲引力干扰的事情？
So what can you tell me about this gravitational disturbance?
为什么你想知道？
Why do you want to know?
我觉得这件事和我爸有关
I think my dad has something to do with it.
等等  你爸是谁？
Wait, who's your dad?
约翰·古斯比
John Goodspeed.
你爸是约翰·古斯比？
Your dad was John Goodspeed?
那我记起来了
Now I remember!
五年前  就是你这个家伙  坚持要我请你一杯
Five years ago, you're the guy who kept asking me for a drink,
结果轰掉了92艘绝统巡航船和一家墨西哥家族餐馆
then blew up 92 Imperium Cruisers and a small Mexican family restaurant!
对  对  对  就是我
Yes, yes, yes! That's me!
你还是记得我的嘛！
You do remember me!
记得啊
I do.
把你的手指移开  不然小心手指抽筋
Now get that finger out of my face, or I'll snap it off.
我好喜欢听你说话
I like how you speak words.
Aah!